<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<Root>
	<LanguageName>
		<eng>English</eng>
	</LanguageName>
	<Languages>eng</Languages>
	<Quest>
		<C2_FabricatorGeneral_Campaign>
			<node1>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Inquisitor, how socially proactive of you to visit me.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node1>
			<node10>
				<Desc>
					<eng>How? You said it was a classified investigation.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node10>
			<node11>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am the Fabricator-General of a Forge Word. I have my methods. I have an informant in the retinue of the Inquisitor in charge, stationed on the ship of a certain Captain van Wynter. We could both benefit from the Archeotech secrets in that monastery.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node11>
			<node12>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will accept your offer, Fabricator-General. I will travel to the coordinates of the “Martyr” immediately.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node12>
			<node2>
				<Desc>
					<eng>You contacted me and promised me information.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node2>
			<node3>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A straightforward approach. Most commendable. I accessed the digital scrolls on your non-classified investigations and noticed the main object of your interest, and this was confirmed by your recent visit to the Sanctum.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node3>
			<node4>
				<Desc>
					<eng>What dominant interest are you referring to?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node4>
			<node5>
				<Desc>
					<eng>You are actively seeking Tech-Relics of Uther Tiberius, the infamous Inquisitor excommunicated for potentially heretical studies. I have information that could significantly advance your pursuit.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node5>
			<node6>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Are you offering me additional information on the Xenarite sect?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node6>
			<node7>
				<Desc>
					<eng>That sect was terminated a long time ago on. I have more valuable information for you. The “Martyr”, the wandering fortress-monastery of Uther Tiberius, long thought to be lost, has returned to the Caligari Sector from the Immaterium.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node7>
			<node8>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A thorough study of the ship could reward me with precious inormation.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node8>
			<node9>
				<Desc>
					<eng>The problem is that the “Martyr” is currently under a highly classified Inquisitorial investigation, which even I have no word on. Your credentials, on the other hand, would grant you access. I have the current coordinates of the ship.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node9>
		</C2_FabricatorGeneral_Campaign>
	</Quest>
</Root>
