<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<Root>
	<LanguageName>
		<eng>English</eng>
	</LanguageName>
	<Languages>eng</Languages>
	<Quest>
		<C2_OrdoHereticus>
			<node1>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I hope our little misunderstanding in the past won't cast a shadow on our relations, Inquisitor.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node1>
			<node10>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Yes?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node10>
			<node11>
				<Desc>
					<eng>It also felt like a waste on a cosmic scale. Perhaps we should have kept some of Bile's specimen. Replicating such a formidable weapon could have turned the tide against the Ruinous Powers and redeemed mankind.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node11>
			<node2>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Let bygones be bygones, Inquisitor Krabart. Still, I expected more from an Inquisitor of the Ordo Hereticus.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node2>
			<node3>
				<Desc>
					<eng>It is an understandable, but deeply misguided expectation. If you spend your waking hours hunting for heretics, traitors and mutant aberrations you tend to… adopt some of their methods. It's regrettable, but also inevitable.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node3>
			<node4>
				<Desc>
					<eng>We should aim to have higher standards, Inquisitor Krabart.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node4>
			<node5>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I understand your reasoning, Inquisitor Krabart. More than you think.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node5>
			<node6>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A child's idea of morality! The Galaxy is burning and the Imperium is struggling against impossible odds. The end justifies the means, don't you think?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node6>
			<node7>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Once I stumbled on an interesting quote in an old scroll, probably predating even the Dark Age of Technology. Something about gazing into the abyss… but I digress.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node7>
			<node8>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Do you think we have made a mistake?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node8>
			<node9>
				<Desc>
					<eng>With the Alpha Pariah? Interesting that you bring it up. I was contemplating the same question recently. Sending the "Martyr" and the Alpha Pariah into the Abyss was the most reasonable way to deal with the Dark Nexus. On the other hand…</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node9>
		</C2_OrdoHereticus>
	</Quest>
</Root>
