<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<Root>
	<LanguageName>
		<eng>English</eng>
	</LanguageName>
	<Languages>eng</Languages>
	<Quest>
		<DLC_Forgotten_Arsenal>
			<node1>
				<Desc>
					<eng>By the Emperor! Is this a real vox broadcast? Or are you only a figment of my imagination after the decades of solitude?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node1>
			<node10>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will take care of the problem.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node10>
			<node11>
				<Desc>
					<eng>When I find the time, I will return.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node11>
			<node12>
				<Desc>
					<eng>[ff4a64a7][Mission info][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node12>
			<node13>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A large group “vermin” - heretical void nomads - have taken up residence in one of the vaults of the repository. This is a straight up cleansing operation.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node13>
			<node14>
				<Desc>
					<eng>&lt;BACK&gt;</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node14>
			<node15>
				<Desc>
					<eng>You have eliminated the vermin. Praise be! We seem to have a new problem, though. The sensors show intruders in the eastern wing, looting the stacks.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node15>
			<node19>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A rogue Astra Militarum warband is looting in the repository, doubtlessly looking for weapons. They must be stopped without too much collateral damage.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node19>
			<node2>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am an agent of the Inquisition and I demand to know who you are, or there will be consequences.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node2>
			<node21>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Did you kill those invaders, Inquisitor? I hope that the sacred scrolls were not damaged... Now there is just the matter of the Onyx Gate.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node21>
			<node22>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Elaborate.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node22>
			<node23>
				<Desc>
					<eng>It is an alien artifact, stored in the special vault by the agents of the Inquisition. The Drukhari used it to stage raiding campaigns from time to time, I believe, and as it turns out, it is still active. I’m yearning to catalogue the contents of the vault, but I dare not approach until the Dark Eldar has been dealt with.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node23>
			<node27>
				<Desc>
					<eng>The Drukhari use a forgotten Webway gate in the repository to launch realspace raids. They must be dealt with.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node27>
			<node29>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Welcome, Inquisitor. Have you come to cleanse the repository?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node29>
			<node3>
				<Desc>
					<eng>My hallucinations are usually not this intimidating.  You must be real then.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node3>
			<node4>
				<Desc>
					<eng>So who would you be?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node4>
			<node43>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Excellent news, Inquisitor! I shall begin cataloguing the special vault immediately. I can also provide access to the inventory of the repository at a discount price.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node43>
			<node44>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Do you really want to sell artifacts to me?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node44>
			<node45>
				<Desc>
					<eng>My last standing orders, which I received 273 standard years and 47 days ago, are to catalogue and maintain this repository as well as acquiring funds for the upkeep of this station by means of trade.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node45>
			<node46>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Welcome! Did you come to trade?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node46>
			<node47>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Show me your inventory.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node47>
			<node48>
				<Desc>
					<eng>See you later.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node48>
			<node5>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am Korvid-509-Theta. I have been entrusted with the care and maintenance of this repository, Administratum Storage-annexe HS-1011.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node5>
			<node51>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Thanks for shopping!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node51>
			<node6>
				<Desc>
					<eng>What sort of repository is this?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node6>
			<node7>
				<Desc>
					<eng>A universal repository, storing codexes, scrolls, paraphernalia and artifacts.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node7>
			<node8>
				<Desc>
					<eng>In the name of the Emperor, I require access to the repository and its contents.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node8>
			<node9>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Certainly, Inquisitor. However, some sections have been infested by vermin and I’m afraid I haven’t been able to get rid of them. I humbly ask you to deal with them.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node9>
		</DLC_Forgotten_Arsenal>
	</Quest>
</Root>
