<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<Root>
	<LanguageName>
		<eng>English</eng>
	</LanguageName>
	<Languages>eng</Languages>
	<Quest>
		<merciful_agony>
			<node1>
				<Desc>
					<eng>MAIN CONVERSATION BODY</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node1>
			<node10>
				<Desc>
					<eng>An Adeptus Mechanicus fortress that tends to the agents of the Inquisition? How?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node10>
			<node11>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Due to the unexplained phenomena commonly referred to as “Caligari Warpsurges” and other factors which are classified and even a fleeting understanding of said factors could be sentenced by death on your clearance level, the Caligari Conclave has entered into a close collaboration with some Cult Mechanicus chapters in the Sector.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node11>
			<node12>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I require more details.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node12>
			<node13>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I want to enhance my abilities through sanctioned bio-augmentation. \n[ff4a64a7][+1 Attribute point to distribute - Cost: 10000 Caligari Credit, 150 Fate][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node13>
			<node14>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I need a thorough genetical recalibration in the transcendence chambers.\n[ff4a64a7][+2 Skill points to distribute - Cost: 25000 Caligari Credit, 100 Fate][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node14>
			<node15>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I require a new component for my Inoculator.\n[ff4a64a7][Removes debuffs when used - Cost: 50000 Caligari Credit][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node15>
			<node16>
				<Desc>
					<eng>That is indeed true. \nThere was a security breach in Ward B where Subject #9 was undergoing preventive amputation. Note: Subject #9 is an agent returning with a shard of unknown substance buried in his flesh. A power surge cut all connections while sensors indicated the appearance of Warp entities. The area has been sealed off since then.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node16>
			<node17>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll deal with this. Have your Tech-Priest stand by to inload the detailed fact sheet to my ship.  [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node17>
			<node18>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I can't deal with this right now. I have other urgent matters to attend to.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node18>
			<node19>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I don't have authority to overrule any decisions made by the agents of the Inquisition. Consequently I must accept your decision.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node19>
			<node2>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I have questions for you and I require answers.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node2>
			<node20>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Improvement through modificiations blessed by the Omnissiah is always the right path to take.  [ff4a64a7][+1 Attribute point gained][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node20>
			<node21>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Excellent. After a thorough purge of the organs and the mind, the rites of genetic transmutation will be initiated. Omnissiah be with you! [ff4a64a7][+2 Skill points gained][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node21>
			<node22>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will dispatch your request to the appropriate crafter-monks. [ff4a64a7][New Inoculator component gained][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node22>
			<node23>
				<Desc>
					<eng>TECHNICAL LINES CONTAINER</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node23>
			<node24>
				<Desc>
					<eng>&lt;BACK&gt;</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node24>
			<node25>
				<Desc>
					<eng>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node25>
			<node26>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am Agrippa 723-Theta, in the holy service of the Omnissiah. This research station is also a blessed chapel for sanctioned transmutation. How can we assist you?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node26>
			<node27>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Omnissiah be with you! I am Agrippa 723-Theta on a special assignment to the Caligari Conclave and this is an Adeptus Mechanicus research sanctum. Tell me what you need.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node27>
			<node28>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am the Metasurgeon of the Holy Ordo of the Adeptus Mechanicus. You are now authorised to access these sacred halls of genetic augmentation. How may we help?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node28>
			<node29>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am Genetor Agrippa 723-Theta. My med-serfs stand ready with the proper rites of evisceration, blessed scalpels and sacred ointments. What is the purpose of your visit?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node29>
			<node3>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I want something from you.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node3>
			<node30>
				<Desc>
					<eng>This is Metasurgeon Agrippa 723-Theta speaking. I will personally supervise your treatment and my lips will sing blessed litanies during your blissfully agonizing treatment. How can I serve you?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node30>
			<node31>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I need you to clarify the reasons for your visit in more detail.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node31>
			<node32>
				<Desc>
					<eng>That is correct. \nRoutine sweeps indicate that an unspecified number Warp-entities must have slipped through the containment protocols activated around Ward B during the sanctioned Inquisitorial purge of the premises and have been dormant on Sub-Deck Alpha until now.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node32>
			<node33>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll deal with this. Have your Tech-Priest stand by to inload the detailed fact sheet to my ship. [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node33>
			<node34>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I can't deal with this right now. I have other urgent matters to attend to.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node34>
			<node35>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I don't have authority to overrule any decisions made by the agents of the Inquisition. Consequently I must accept your decision.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node35>
			<node36>
				<Desc>
					<eng>That is correct. \nConnection was lost with Level B4-Z. Sensors picked up Warp-energies that indicate the opening of a Chaos Portal centred on an unknown individual. The heat signatures of said individual are consistent with the data on Subject #9 who disappeared during the purge of Ward B and never been confirmed dead.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node36>
			<node37>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll deal with this. Have your Tech-Priest stand by to inload the detailed fact sheet to my ship.  [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node37>
			<node38>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I can't deal with this right now. I have other urgent matters to attend to.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node38>
			<node39>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I don't have authority to overrule any decisions made by the agents of the Inquisition. Consequently I must accept your decision.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node39>
			<node4>
				<Desc>
					<eng>It has come to my knowledge that you might require the assistance of the Inquisition. [ff4a64a7][New mission][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node4>
			<node40>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Regarding that mission...</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node40>
			<node41>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I must ask you to be more specific.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node41>
			<node42>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I put an end to the security breach in Ward B. For all relevant details you should apply for a copy of my official report through the appropriate channels.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node42>
			<node43>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Mission accomplished. Proceeding to the next complication. We have a new assignment for you.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node43>
			<node44>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I've dealt with the Warp-entities on Sub-Deck Alpha. For all relevant details you should apply for a copy of my official report through the appropriate channels.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node44>
			<node45>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Impressive success ratio. Note that new complications have arisen in the interim. We need further assistance.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node45>
			<node46>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I've terminated the infestation connected to Subject #9. For all relevant details you should apply for a copy of my official report through the appropriate channels.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node46>
			<node47>
				<Desc>
					<eng>We have found your cooperation most valuable. Allow us to compensate   your work with our medical expertise. [ff4a64a7][Subdermal Mesh perk gained][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node47>
			<node48>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will make another attempt at that task.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node48>
			<node49>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Determination is a much admirable trait in the service of the Imperium.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node49>
			<node5>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I can provide you information unless it requires Code Theta-7 clearance level. Ask.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node5>
			<node50>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll go now. [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node50>
			<node51>
				<Desc>
					<eng>However... before I go, I still need to take care of something.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node51>
			<node52>
				<Desc>
					<eng>As you wish.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node52>
			<node53>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will make another attempt at that task.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node53>
			<node54>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Determination is a gift for the chosen of the Imperium.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node54>
			<node55>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll go now. [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node55>
			<node56>
				<Desc>
					<eng>However, before I go, I still need to take care of something.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node56>
			<node57>
				<Desc>
					<eng>As you wish.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node57>
			<node58>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will make another attempt at that task.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node58>
			<node59>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I couldn't but notice the level of your determination.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node59>
			<node6>
				<Desc>
					<eng>What is the purpose of this place?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node6>
			<node60>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I'll go now. [Start Mission]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node60>
			<node61>
				<Desc>
					<eng>However, before I go, I still need to take care of something.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node61>
			<node62>
				<Desc>
					<eng>As you wish.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node62>
			<node63>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I must leave now.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node63>
			<node64>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Due to insufficient funds we must decline your request.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node64>
			<node65>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Due to insufficient funds we must decline your request.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node65>
			<node66>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Due to insufficient funds we must decline your request.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node66>
			<node7>
				<Desc>
					<eng>The Merciful Agony MCXII is an Adeptus Mechanicus research sanctum focusing on the implementations of ancient sacred texts about genetical modifications. We have been also assigned to assist the Inquisitorial agents of the Caligari Sector. It is a very beneficial cooperation. The agents of the Ordo can serve the Emperor better, while we are collecting valuable data on the effects of the treatments that help us lower the mortality rate and the chance of repugnant mutation.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node7>
			<node8>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I need some more information on the Genetors.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node8>
			<node9>
				<Desc>
					<eng>We are one of the Holy Orders among the priesthood of the Adeptus Mechanicus. We focus on genetics, we devote ourselves to the study of biology and organic anatomy. If you seek non-cybernetic augmentation, you have come to the right place.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node9>
		</merciful_agony>
	</Quest>
</Root>
