<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<Root>
	<LanguageName>
		<eng>English</eng>
	</LanguageName>
	<Languages>eng</Languages>
	<Quest>
		<unholy_cathedral>
			<node1>
				<Desc>
					<eng>MAIN CONVERSATION BODY</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node1>
			<node10>
				<Desc>
					<eng>After decades of thorough research we located the moon. Our delegation came here to consecrate the cathedral. We knew that something was wrong, but in our pride and arrogance we went too deep under that forsaken cathedral and excavated something that we thought to be the sacred bones. Instead we woke up the slumbering powers of a corrupted artefact… may the mercy of the Emperor be with us!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node10>
			<node11>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Your request for Inquisitorial assistance has been registered. Keep vigil until we make the arrangements to deal with the situation.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node11>
			<node12>
				<Desc>
					<eng>TECHNICAL LINE CONTAINER</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node12>
			<node13>
				<Desc>
					<eng>&lt;BACK&gt;</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node13>
			<node14>
				<Desc>
					<eng>----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node14>
			<node15>
				<Desc>
					<eng>By the grace of the Emperor, an Inquisitorial agent at last! This unholy moon is teeming with the filth of the Immaterium, bending their will to the power of an evil artefact. You must stem their tide before it all spirals out of control!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node15>
			<node16>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Sinners, we all are! We have brought this upon us! We should have never entered that forsaken ruin. I beg for your mercy and your willingness to hold the tide of darkness until your inevitable death grants you eternal glory!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node16>
			<node17>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Emperor preserve us! Know that you are facing the most glorious task of your life-long servitude. Look at that gaping wound on the face of that moon. It is endlessly spitting out spawns of Chaos and you must enter that pit to give them death!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node17>
			<node18>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Emperor, have mercy on us! A swarm of abominations are sweeping over this accursed moon! You must enter the accursed cathedral and stand your ground between hell and mankind!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node18>
			<node19>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Act before it is too late! Face the horde of unnameable monsters bringing death and destruction to everything. They must be stopped before they can spread over the whole moon.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node19>
			<node2>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I will accept the task. Pray to the God-Emperor while I stand my ground in that unholy cathedral.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node2>
			<node20>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Please, do something! You must do something right now!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node20>
			<node21>
				<Desc>
					<eng>[ff4a64a7][Mission info][/ff4a64a7]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node21>
			<node22>
				<Desc>
					<eng>[This is an endless mission. It consists of multiple waves. The longer you survive, the better rewards you get. Survive for over 5 minutes to win the mission.]</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node22>
			<node23>
				<Desc>
					<eng>[This is an endless mission. It consists of multiple waves. The longer you survive, the better rewards you get. Survive for over 5 minutes to win the mission.]\n\nNOT AVAILABLE IN COOP MODE</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node23>
			<node3>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I want you to answer my questions first.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node3>
			<node4>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Yes, of course. But I must warn you... we are running out of time!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node4>
			<node5>
				<Desc>
					<eng>Who are you and what are you doing here?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node5>
			<node6>
				<Desc>
					<eng>What is this place?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node6>
			<node7>
				<Desc>
					<eng>What happened here?</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node7>
			<node8>
				<Desc>
					<eng>I am only a priest of the Adeptus Ministorium, a survivor of a holy delegation assembled by the esteemed Cardinal Damianus himself. We came out here, to the darkest reach of the void to find the scared relic of the patron saint of our home system. But what we found instead was something that defies words!</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node8>
			<node9>
				<Desc>
					<eng>During the Great Crusade the patron of our system, Saint Aelfred came to this moon and defeated a Daemon Prince in a battle that cost him his life as well. A cathedral was built over his bones, but then, for unknown reasons, the location of the moon was purged from all Ministorium archives.</eng>
				</Desc>
			</node9>
		</unholy_cathedral>
	</Quest>
</Root>
